despair.com 2014-06-30

# Despair, Inc. - Privacy Policy

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/details.html) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see theYahoo! Privacy Policy for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

_Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!,click here._

As you browse Despair, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with glennz.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number.

## Despair, Inc.® respects your privacy/buying power.

Despair, Inc.® does not rent or sell personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies. Frankly, most of our customers aren't exactly the kinds of people you want to share with others. Despair, Inc.® does, however, share information with various third-party companies that it hires to perform certain services on Despair's behalf. Despair, Inc.® does not authorize these vendors to share your personal information with anyone, apart from those required to perform their respective contracted services. These services include, but may not be limited to, the following:

  * **Fulfillment:**
  * To further eliminate non-Executive jobs at Despair, Inc.®, we have contracted out order fulfillment to a different company who picks, packs and ships customer orders.
  * **Shipping:**
  * Name and address data are made available to shippers to enable them to deliver customers' purchases.
  * **Email List Management:**
  * Despair, Inc.® contracts with a list management service to administer its Wailing List™.
  * **Printing:**
  * Despair, Inc.® periodically mails catalogs or other materials current and potential future customers. Therefore, Despair, Inc.® must share name and address data with the printer.
  * **Catalog list administration:**
  * Despair, Inc.® occasionally purchases the names and addresses of people from less scrupulous retailers than ourselves. This process requires that we share the name and address data of those who have asked to have our catalogs sent to them to identify duplicates. The catalog list administration is not allowed to share our customer list with any other of their clients.

In addition to the above, Despair, Inc.® may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide customer information to governmental authorities. We will disclose customer information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. Despair, Inc.® fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities (e.g. the fraudulent use of the Despair Frownie logo in email exchanges). We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities (e.g. credit card fraud) that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.
